Oh, it’s been a while!
お、久しぶり!
long time no see!
久しぶり!
Dami-chan, it’s been a really long time!
ダミちゃん、めちゃくちゃ久しぶりやんか!
hey!
ね!
I thought for sure that you would come today!
絶対、今日来てくれへん、思った!
Let's go!
行くよー!
Really?
ほんまに?
Well, I was really looking forward to today.
いやー、今日めっちゃ楽しみにしてたよ、
I!
俺!
Well, we were looking forward to it too.
ね、うちも楽しみにしてた
Is that so?
そんな?
Yeah.
うん
I thought I'd definitely come today, because...
今日絶対来へんと思ったから、 だって、
We've been ignoring you for a long time.
ずっと無視しとったよ、俺ら
I'm not ignoring you!
無視してないよ!
Are you ignoring me?
無視してない?
I'm a little busy at university.
ちょっと大学が忙しくて
Yeah, I've been busy.
うん、忙しかったよ
Eh, but it's true that I entered it.
えー、でも入ったことやもんね、確かに
Is that so?
そうなのー
I see.
そっか
Dami-chan, until what time can you go today?
ダミちゃんさ、今日ってさ、何時まで行けるの?
I have to write a report today, so
今日、ちょっとレポート書かなきゃいけないから、
I might have to go home early.
早めに帰んなきゃいけないかも
Well, I don't like it.
えー、 嫌 だ なー
Because I'm busy.
忙しいから
I think we should go shopping or something.
買い物とかもしようかなと思うんだけど、
It looks a little cold.
ちょっと寒そうやもんね
It's cold, just a little bit.
寒いね、ちょっとだけ
Because it's cold today.
今日寒いから
Is there a good way to pray?
なんかさ、 祈り方いいかいしょ?
Eh, okay?
え、いいのー?
Eh, then what do you get?
え、じゃあ何得?
Eh, I want it.
え、欲しい
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
Shall I buy something then?
じゃあ何か買おうか
Yay!
やったー
I can even smell it.
匂いすらいだけどなー
How to buy.
買い方
Try buying it.
買ってみてよ
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいね
Yeah.
うん
Oh, definitely do it?
え、絶対にする?
Is that so?
そういうこと?
Yeah.
うん
This suited me so well.
めっちゃ似合っとった、これ
It's cute.
かわいいよ
This is really cute.
ほんとにかわいいな、これ
Thank you.
ありがとうー
Were you happy?
嬉しかった?
Yeah, I'm really happy.
うん、めっちゃ嬉しい
He's cute.
かわいいやつで
But what?
でも、何?
Because Shine was pressed.
シャイン押されたからさ
I can do it from what I hear.
聞くばりできるね
What?
なんて?
I can do it from what I hear.
聞くばりできるね
That's cute hair.
かわいい髪やね
Just cute hair.
かわいい髪だけで
I'm so happy.
めっちゃ嬉しい
It's limited.
限定ですよ
Thank you.
ありがとうー
It's new.
新しくなってきたなー
That's amazing.
すごいー
すごい ねー
What's white?
白いの何?
chair?
椅子?
Is this a chair?
これ椅子か
Eh, what do you think?
え、どう?
Chair.
椅 子
It's a bit stiff though.
なんかちょっと硬いけど
I think it's a chair.
椅子だと思う
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごい
え、すげー
Full of shapes.
形いっぱい
Isn't it like a cloud?
雲みたいじゃない?
Is it a cloud?
雲かな?
cute.
かわいい
chair.
椅子
Eh, a chair?
え、椅子?
hard?
硬い?
I guess it's a little soft.
ちょっとだけ柔らかいかな
It was wider.
もっと広かったね
I'm not sitting next to you either.
俺も横で一緒に居ないんだけどね
I'm alone.
一人よー
Ah, but it's not very fashionable.
あ、でもめっちゃオシャレやねんけどね
Because it has an adult atmosphere.
大人の雰囲気するから
It's a bit lacking for inner school students and An-chan at inner school.
内学生、内学のあんちゃんにはちょっとまだないからね
Was it early?
早かったか
There's something I've been wondering about for a long time,
ずっと気になったことあるんだけど、
good?
いい?
Listen.
聞いて
Awesome.
すげー
It's not pants though.
パンツじゃないけどね
誰?
this.
これ
this?
これ?
Ah, the black one.
あ、黒いやつ
A black one.
黒いやつ
Yes, this is it, this.
そう、これなんだ、これ
It's the one that comes with the skirt.
スカートについてきてるやつだから
Since everyone is wearing skirts, I was wondering if you could show me.
みんなスカート履いてるからさ、見せてくれるかなって思って
I can barely see it.
ギリギリ見えない
It's quite nice, it looks chocolatey.
結構ね、いい感じの、チョコチョコ見える
Oh, really?
あ、本当に?
Wait, did I guess?
ちょっとじゃあ、俺が当てたのか?
Yeah.
うん
A glimpse.
チラッ
Ah, correct.
あ、正解
Eh, correct?
え、正解?
Seriously?
まじで?
Did you see it?
見えてたの?
Yeah, just a glimpse.
うん、ちょっとチラッと
If you answered correctly, is there a reward?
正解したの、ご褒美ある?
Reward?
ご褒美?
Is there a reward?
ご褒美ある?
Hmm, I'll think about it.
う ーん、考えとく
No, think about it now.
いや、今考えて
now?
今?
Think now.
今 考えて今
Ah, then those who answer correctly will be shown the real thing.
あ、じゃあ正解者には、なんと本物を見せてくれるという、
Does that person have the correct answer?
そういう正解者にはある?
See you later.
後でね
Can I do it later?
後でいいの?
Oh, seriously?
え、まじで?
Okay.
いいよ
Eh, let's do it quickly?
え、早くやろう?
I made a promise.
約束しちゃった
I'll see about that later.
あとでちょっとあれね
Correct, let me show you a little bit.
正解、ちょっと見せてくれます
Announcing the correct answer?
正解発表?
I will let you know the correct answer.
正解発表させてくれます
There aren't any people around here.
ここらへんやったらさ、人全然おらん
There isn't one.
いないね
There's no one there.
誰もいないやん
There's really no one there.
ほ んとに人いない
He's not there.
いないじゃん
Wouldn't it be nice to do it here?
ここやったらいいんじゃないの?
Is this okay?
ここでいい?
Should I do it here?
ここやったらいい?
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
It's not white.
白じゃない
Wow, so pale.
うわ、めっちゃ色白い
I really miss you.
めっちゃ会えないよ
I wanted to see it.
見たかった
見たかったな
Just a little, just a little.
ちょっとさ、ちょっと
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Just a little, just a little.
ちょっとさ、ちょっと
Yeah.
うん
Very
めっちゃ
It's small.
ち っちゃい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしい?
Ah, beautiful.
あー、綺麗
It's so beautiful.
めちゃくちゃ綺麗ね
めちゃくちゃ綺麗
The shape is also very beautiful.
形もめっちゃ綺麗し
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
You can't nod off in a place like this.
こんなところでうなずしないもんね
You don't nod.
うなずしないね
There's someone over there, look.
あそこに人いるよ、ほら
I feel like I'm being watched.
見られてる気がする
picture?
え?
I feel like I'm being watched.
見られてる気がする
Do you feel like you're being watched?
見られてる気がする?
Yeah.
うん
Someone was in there just now, is it okay?
今誰か入ってたけど大丈夫?
Because it was in there.
入ってたからよ
I went in.
入ってちゃった
Please come back to the bathroom for a moment.
ちょっとトイレまた入ってきてください
Really?
ほんとに?
Her shy face is so cute.
照れてる顔めっちゃ可愛い
Damn it.
くそがったい
Okay, so let's go down a little bit.
よし、じゃあちょっと下行くよ
Yeah.
うん
I'd like to put my underwear down.
下着をさ、下にさめたいんだけど
Biccha biccha.
びっちゃびっちゃ
It didn't happen, did it?
かなかったんじゃないの?
I'm really going home today.
ほんまに帰っちゃうな、今日
I'm going home.
帰っちゃうね
Say it out loud.
声でしてて
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Is it coming out in Rufan's ears?
ちょっとルファンの耳に出てきてるんですか?
It might take a while to get used to it.
ちょっと慣れてくれへんかも
Yeah.
うん
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃうまい
This is so delicious.
めちゃうまいな、これ
what?
なに?
Messed up?
めちゃめちゃ?
Yeah.
うん
If you look over here, slide it.
こっち見たら滑らしてほら
When I see your face, keep looking at me
顔見たらずっとずっと見て
I want it.
ほ しい
Chill and chill below.
下でチルチルしてほら
Down, down, down.
下だ、下だ、下だして
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It felt so good, so I spit out the bottom.
気持ちよかったから、下を吐き出してほら
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
I'm also vomiting potash.
カリとかも吐いてるんですよ
That's how they do it.
そちら、そちらはそうやるの
Oh, Emi-chan, Emi-chan.
ああ、エミちゃんエミちゃん
It would be bad if you licked me.
舐めてもらったら悪いからさ
Can I have Emi-chan lick me a little too?
ちょっとエミちゃんも舐めてもらっていい?
Yes, that's totally fine.
はい、全然いいわけですよ
You can lend me the funds.
財資貸していいから
That's right.
そうだ
I'm sorry for hitting you so hard.
バチに叩いちゃってごめんな
Sai.
さい
Please take a shower.
シ ャワー洗ってなよ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Look at it, let's lick it.
見て、チルチル舐めてやろう
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
Emi-chan, Emi-chan, Emi-chan,
エミちゃん、エミちゃん、エミちゃん、
Emi-chan, Emi-chan.
エミちゃん、エミちゃん
Ah, ah, ah.
ああ, ああ,ああ.
My breath was coming in.
息 すぎが入ってきた
Emi-chan, are you breathing too much?
エミちゃん息すぎやろ?
I can keep breathing.
息きが続かんじゃう
Emi-chan, it's only one day.
エミちゃん、1日やねんわ
Let's put a lot of this in.
これいっぱい入ってやろう
Oh wait a minute.
ああ ちょっと待ってよ